Hello friends welcome back to my channel today
I am bringing a new job opportunity for you guys
this opportunity has come
from ICICI Lombard ICICI
Lombard is hiring
for the post of insurance agent ICICI
sells different policies under different names so it
sells health insurance under the name Lombard so
what happens in health insurance generally
see if you work in any life insurance company then
now you
cannot sell life insurance of any other company but as much as
I know in health insurance
you can confirm as much as
I know now you can
sell health insurance of any other company also if you are already
employed somewhere in an insurance company then also you
can do health insurance anywhere else at any time so
you can apply anywhere so
this is ringing the insurance agent's
remote whatever your qualification is nothing has been given here no
details have been given here
they have
given only the contact number of pickle so everyone  I have
given the number of the candidate, so this is also a very good
thing because sometimes
even after making the video, people have some queries
whether it is fake or if they have this doubt, so
now you can directly call here,
okay, you can note down this number, I will also call it
8-89956377, okay,
88956377, okay, it is a very easy number and
you can also WhatsApp on this, it is written hello,
this is de health insurance agent
profile interest rate candidates call and
whatsapp on date, so you can also apply
and instead of applying directly,
you can also ask from here, okay, whatever
queries you have, okay, apart from this,
they have
not written about the qualification here, but as far as I am making this video, till now it was said
that 10th and 12th were being asked,
but now if we look at the middle, in all the
videos that I have made, graduate has been asked,
okay, so most probably in this
also you should go for graduate, okay, it may be
intermediate also, we
cannot do that because  It is not written here but
my qualification can be graduate,
if you need any confirmation then
call on the contact number here, I actually
make videos at night, that is why
I could not call achar, after confirming I would have
told you myself
about the qualification etc., ok then
note down the number
88956377, ok you can call on this
and I hope you liked this vacancy
and if you like my channel then
subscribe to it because I keep
providing such latest job updates,
thanks for watching my channel by